{"data":[{"question":"More than 1,000 runner participated in this year's Manchester marathon.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"More than","b":"1,000 runner","c":"in","d":"marathon","answer":"2","explain":"- 1000 runner-> 1000 runners","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The way he took everything she does for granted really annoyed her.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"took","b":"does","c":"granted","d":"annoyed","answer":"2","explain":"- Does-> did\/had done","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The personnel promised him that she would not tell anyone that he has been in prison.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"promised","b":"would","c":"that","d":"has been","answer":"4","explain":"- Has been-> had been","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"In my arrival home, I realised that I had left my book in the room.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"arrival","c":"realised","d":"had left","answer":"1","explain":"- On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"My father is going to be really angry what he finds out that I have lost the car key.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"really","b":"what","c":"that","d":"have lost","answer":"2","explain":"- What-> when","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"People whose live in glass houses shouldn't throw stones.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"whose","b":"glass","c":"shouldn't","d":"stones","answer":"1","explain":"- Whose-> who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"He spent most of his times traveling around the world and now he is writing about his experiences.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"times","b":"traveling","c":"is writing","d":"experiences","answer":"1","explain":"- Times-> time","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"I wrote to him last week but so far I received no reply to my letter.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wrote","b":"so far","c":"received","d":"to","answer":"3","explain":"- Received-> have received","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"If the earth suddenly stopped to spin, we would all fly off it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"to spin","c":"would","d":"off","answer":"2","explain":"- To spin-> to spinning","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"This building will have finished by the end of 2000.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"will","b":"have finished","c":"by","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"- Have finished-> have been finished","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}